Hey, excuse me. Can you get off my front
porch?
>> This is not your front porch. I actually
rented this place and I know the code.
Hello and welcome to a week in my life
in Los Angeles. [music] Yes, guys, I'm
here for work so I want to show you what
it's like being a small business owner
and being slightly bi-coastal because I
have a lot of stuff going on. We're
staying at this lovely Airbnb so I want
to show you guys around. But first,
there is kind of a crazy reason that I'm
in LA. Wait, literally what could it be?
What could it literally be? Okay, well,
it's something to think about and
something that I will get into shortly.
Welcome in. This is our gorgeous living
room. That's my mom.
>> Hi.
>> Down here, we have a beautiful and
spacious kitchen, okay?
>> Wow.
>> I love the floors.
>> This is so [music] gorgeous.
>> Look at the stained glass.
>> Welcome to the primary bedroom. This is
where my mom will in fact be staying.
>> And look, I love the mirror.
>> This is my sister Amber.
>> Okay, continuing on.
>> Come into the bathroom. I think this is
my favorite room in the entire house.
Like, are you kidding? This is so
beautiful and it's so bright and look at
the bathtub. Pause. Perhaps what is this
on the counter? Guys, there is something
that I have been keeping secret for
literally almost a year now. The biggest
and most important and just craziest
collab of all time between another brand
and Nami. And if you guys recognize this
gloss balm right here, you would know
that this is a collab between Fenty
Beauty and Nami Matcha.
Are we serious right now? So, this will
be on the Nami website.
>> [laughter and gasps]
>> Oh my goodness. This is such a dream.
So, also, there's really a ice cream
man.
>> He wants some Fenty.
>> Okay, well, first of all, something that
I love about both Fenty and Nami is that
they're both women-owned brands and I
think both brands have done some pretty
epic stuff in their own right, whether
it's Fenty having such an inclusive
range of shades, or you know, at Na'vi,
we are women API owned brand, so we are
making moves in
>> [music]
>> the food and beverage industry. So guys,
imagine me and Fenty, boom, we have a
baby.
>> Rockabye baby, rockabye Fenty in the
>> Rockabye Fenty
rockabye Fenty
>> in the pink box.
>> If you have never tried Fenty's gloss
balm, it is literally the best lip gloss
of all time. I'm wearing it right now.
This is my favorite shade. It's in the
shade Fussy. Ooh, kind of like soft
lighter pink. Just the littlest like bit
of shimmer.
>> Bro, not even capping, not even glazing,
that is the prettiest gloss I've ever
seen.
>> No way.
>> Thank you. Okay, and then we also of
course have our Na'vi strawberry matcha,
which is our most sought after matcha.
We've been sold out for a minute, but
it's finally back in our Fenty collab
package. And then of course, we also
have a little keychain for a keychain
that you can put your gloss balm in.
This is how it comes with like a LITTLE
>> HEY, MICHAELA.
>> [screaming]
>> NO WAY.
>> YES. She's doing the unboxing.
>> It looks like a little creature that I
want to adopt.
>> Perfectly houses your gloss balm.
>> Oh my gosh. Bro, I'm still dead at the
lip gloss. Like you're going to watch
this footage and be like, "Wow, I've
never looked better."
>> Because it's literally the best shade
for everyone, like I swear.
>> Okay, am I getting one of those cuz I
actually want it right now.
>> I don't know if we have enough for you,
sorry.
Speaking of not having enough, guys,
this is a limited edition collab box,
[music] okay? So this is the only time
and place that you will be able to get
it, including our special little fuzzy
keychain with our Fenty and [music]
Na'vi colors. It is launching on August
5th at 3:00 p.m. Eastern time. So if
you're watching the video
>> [music]
>> while supplies last.
We have a surprise for you.
>> Thank you.
Ooh,
very nice.
>> [laughter]
>> It took her a second to realize.
>> That is a really universally beautiful
color.
>> Right.
>> But especially on your lips looks great.
[music]
>> Oh, I love the smell.
>> It smells so good.
>> [snorts and laughter]
>> It's crazy.
>> She did that?
Continuing with the house tour.
>> Here is one of the bedrooms. Very
gorgeous, very huge.
>> I love the artwork.
Can I steal that? Another bathroom.
>> This is something I do not get in New
York City is like literally
Like literally this. Like you see how
there's trees on the window? Like and it
goes like
But look, it's also in this corner.
Look, there I am. But look at how like
>> This is Ashley's room.
>> See this room? And this is going to be
my room.
>> And for me, this is my room.
>> That's the tour and we will continue my
work week later.
>> [music]
>> Good morning.
It is a very big day because today is
our Fenty photo shoot day. That is
obviously one of the reasons why I'm out
here in LA specifically. I wanted to
show you guys all of the behind the
scenes of what kind of goes on for a
shoot like this and I'm going to be the
model.
For the photo shoot. Mom, how does it
feel to have a daughter that is a model?
>> Amazing.
>> But so right now we are heading there,
our shoot location. We have two shoot
locations, but the first one is in Los
Feliz.
>> [music]
>> You think Rihanna's pulling up today?
>> I already texted her. She said she's on
her way.
>> I'm going to start sending her my
Christmas card every year.
>> We're going to try to be best friends.
Like, let's go get coffee, girl. I know
you're dying to hang out with us and our
mom. That'd be great.
>> [laughter]
>> We made it! Okay, we've made it to the
location. What is this, Mom?
>> Schedule, locations, shot list, and
different videos that we have to get.
>> Yeah, and these are like our actual
shots that we're doing. Very cute.
>> And then we have a lot of like Frankie
products and stuff. So cute.
>> Okay, hi guys. We made it on set.
Sitting in the special stool right now
because we are going to be doing a very
crazy hairstyle and my mom is going to
help. Right, Mom?
>> Yes.
>> Yes! This is my unpaid hair stylist.
Starting off the shoot with a mental
breakdown on my part because we wanted
to do Nami Matcha tin hair rollers and
they would not stay in my hair. I was
thinking, "Oh, no. This is going to be a
disaster." Meanwhile, the rest of the
team started taking product photos as I
messed with my hair and eventually gave
up and just decided to shoot with this
cute little pink outfit with my normal
hair instead. And guys, don't be
discouraged about the Nami hair rollers
because as I was shooting all these
photos, my friend Michaela went out on a
mission to buy real hair rollers for me.
Mom and Michaela made these Nami hair
rollers so that hopefully it sticks in
her hair this time. Okay, update. We
really struggled with the hair roller,
so we're shooting other photos first.
Right now we're doing one in the mirror
and the amount of lip gloss that I've
reapplied is actually insane. Wait, do
you guys want to say hi? Only if you
want to. In my vlog.
>> Hi, I'm Manon. I'm the film
photographer.
>> I think you guys know Olivia.
>> I'm just taking social content.
>> I'm Alonzo. I'm the photo assist.
>> I'm Jimena. I'm the production designer.
>> I'm Ashlyn. I'm producing and shooting
on digital.
>> Hey!
>> Michaela's my my hair assistant today.
She's actually just my friend that's
hanging out. Who's this?
>> Who's [laughter] this? It's my mom.
>> It's my mom. Oh, and of course we have
Amber.
Hello. Oh my god, I'm bald. What was so
cute about this shoe is that we worked
with a bunch of Chapman grads, which if
you know, you know, Amber and Andrew
both went to Chapman, and they were so
professional. Like the fact that they
made a call sheet and they listed out
all of the shots we had to get. Wait,
Amber, what did you just say? Apparently
walked by outside I and I missed it cuz
I was in the house. No.
>> Sorry.
>> Who do we have stepping in as the foot
model? Obviously me. I mean
>> Here we go. Foot reveal. Oh, very
gorgeous.
>> Cuz I have a blister on my foot right
there. Keep that away. But I did hear
that Nami's going to be putting a
billboard across Hollywood and it's
going to be my feet. I'm so excited.
Okay, now we have just driven 15 minutes
to our next location. We have about 30
minutes before we're allowed into the
house, so we are doing my hair rollers
in the car because we just did not have
time at the other shoot. So sometimes
you got to go with the flow. So
basically this is the situation. We have
hair rollers that we clamped around the
tin and we're going to see if that gives
some grippiness to my hair. Going up,
mom would always cut my hair, so I
assumed she could also do this.
Did it work?
>> So cute.
>> There's two on my head.
>> [music]
>> Guys, look at my freaking hair that mom
did. It looks amazing. Mom banged this
out [music] in like 20 minutes and it
looks amazing.
>> killed that.
>> She killed it. The back we just like I
[music] have too much hair, so we just
kind of like shoved it all in there, but
it looks fine, I think. I feel like I
have like a crown. Like this is my Nami
crown. Okay, everybody's lit because I
got my hair rollers finally. Kelly's in
Puerto Rico drinking an IVL. I have
matcha in my hair.
This is my dream house as a baby. And
look at our [music] freaking smoothies.
>> Welcome in. Everybody's getting set up.
>> Um, where are we? What is this?
Uh, what are we doing?
>> Mom is so cute.
>> And people live in here. They have cats.
[music]
>> Okay, we're going to be shooting in
here.
>> But look at how cute. It's so decked
out.
>> Oh my god.
>> How is it all the same color [music]
scheme? Like where are they getting all
this pink and teal stuff?
>> Oh.
>> Holy I did not look up. Woah.
>> This is so funny.
>> Who's outside with the fan setting up
these effects?
I don't [music] know why, but me
drinking this smoothie on set is giving
diva. Lol. Anyways, we started off by
shooting some more product shots as I
finished eating [music] my lunch, and
then we got right back into the good
stuff. I'm on the counter, and it might
not look like it, but this was the most
uncomfortable position I've ever been
in. Anything for the photo, though. Say
cheese.
We're shooting mostly with our Fenty
like little fluffy guy right here. If I
didn't say this already, I am so
grateful to have these [music]
opportunities. Collaborating with a
brand like Fenty Beauty that is in the
big leagues is literally so insane to
me, and it wouldn't have been able to do
it without all of you guys' support. So,
from the bottom of my heart, thank you
so [music] much to everyone who has
watched my videos, not me matcha, and
just help me get to where I am today
because this is for real a dream come
true.
>> We did it.
>> Yay.
>> Mom is literally so tired. Let's go take
a look at Mom.
>> Oh, no.
>> Oh, no. She's out cold, bro.
>> Okay, the hair is coming out. My neck
like literally hurts so bad from the
weight.
>> Ooh, nice bang.
>> And that's a wrap. Woo, we did it.
[screaming] Yay.
Thanks, guys.
Celebratory bingsoo with
>> Hi.
>> And our dingus.
>> They called out my name. I put down as
dingus. They said,
"Uh, order for dingus?"
>> [laughter]
>> OMG, OMG, OMG. OMG, OMG, OMG.
This is fire, bro.
>> Really?
>> I didn't even realize it's in a melon.
>> It's so fluffy and like melon.
>> Bro, all the tables opened up. Rotate,
rotate, we need to rotate.
>> Ba ba ba, pit stained by Asher Dingus
and Ander Dingus.
Excuse me, sir, my salary is so low that
I cannot pay I cannot feed my family. Do
you think you could help my pay just by
like 5 cents an hour?
>> [laughter]
>> Good freaking morning. You thought we
only had one good freaking morning. Good
morning.
Good morning. Doing a little interview
show with our friend Nicholas. I think
it's kind of like a Jubilee style video.
>> I'm going to hack into the mainframe.
>> [laughter]
>> Bro, you've been fired.
Pack up your stuff and leave.
>> I'm done.
>> [snorts]
>> You went to the bathroom too long. I
hacked everything. I'm the boss now.
>> Bro, this reminds me of my job.
>> Get out.
>> Wait, what's this?
>> Yes, in the corner.
>> the boss comes in?
>> [laughter]
[music]
>> Wait, can you show them?
No.
Girl, Andu, how did it go?
>> It went amazing.
>> It's so fun.
>> So fun.
>> Well, watch the interview and you can
see Asher's pit stains. Yes. Now we're
out of here.
>> Bye.
>> Bye, Los Angeles.
>> Bye, bro. We'll see you. Nice time.
>> Good morning. And now welcome to a day
in my life in [music] New York City.
Right now I'm heading to a cycling class
and you guys know I like to start my
mornings with a workout class. Every
[music] day I'm running late and then I
pretty much have to jog or even
sometimes run. Anyways, I think starting
with a workout class is such an amazing
way to start your morning because it
gets the hardest part of your day out of
the way and it starts your day with an
amazing boost of endorphins. I feel
healthy, I feel strong and then from
there you can make other amazing
decisions about your day moving forward.
It's just good vibes.
>> [music]
>> I'm home. I have showered and we are now
going to make breakfast together. Step
one, [music] get yourself some black
cherries as well as honey and a nice
little
Oh, GOD damn it. Why does this always
happen?
Take a little bowl of yogurt. Then we're
going to pour some honey right over it.
I like to use a lot of honey. Kind of
difficult, but I'm going to cut my
little cherry in half.
You put it on the yogurt bowl and it
just looks so gorgeous, guys.
Hemp seeds [music] just to make it look
cute. And now we have this adorable
little yogurt bowl. It's high protein,
[music] has some cherries, honey, hemp
seeds.
Feasted.
Okay, now it's matcha time.
Obviously, we're going to be making a
strawberry matcha latte today because I
realized I didn't even make one yet in
the vlog. Hopefully, you can kind of,
you know, smell it and taste it through
the screen. Fenty Beauty's most gorgeous
universal shade that also has the most
delicious scent. Had to reapply because
I ate a lot of my lip gloss when I ate
my yogurt. I'm going to make my most
classic and perfect strawberry matcha
recipe. So, feel free to follow along.
Other items you'll need are a bowl,
sieve, scoop, and a whisk. This is our
golden charm whisk, which you can also
feel free to bundle into your order if
you would like. We need to heat up our
water. This is my kettle and I'm going
to heat it to around 170° F. Now, if you
are a person that likes to weigh your
matcha, you can take out your gram
scale. I'm going to plop my bowl on it
and zero it out. And now that our water
has heated, we're going to bloom our
whisk by just pouring some of the hot
water over the bristles so that the
bristles get softened and they don't
break. And we're going to take a few
scoops of matcha. It'll be about 3 g.
So, if you're weighing it out on your
gram scale, you can do just a couple
grams or you can do 3 g if you would
like. Get a nice
scoop. Okay. Oh, perfectly 3 g.
And then for every gram of matcha,
you're going to add 10 ml of water. So,
it'll be 30 ml of water.
>> [music]
>> And immediately, you can smell the
amazing strawberry aroma. And it has no
sweetener. It's completely natural
flavoring. So, we're just whisking it
back and forth W and M motion. And you
want to have a nice beautiful foam.
Gorgeous. I'm going to add about 10 g of
agave or maple syrup. Then, I'm going to
add just a splash of water to dilute it.
Now it's time for our ice.
Oat milk.
And of course, our matcha.
Guys, want to know what I literally just
realized? I scooped in the matcha and I
forgot to sift it. How do I forget to
sift it every single time? Make sure
that you sift your matcha. It's a nice
little extra step you can do. Luckily,
Na'vi Matcha does not clump very much.
Hence, I forget to sift sometimes. She's
beautiful.
>> [singing]
>> Are you kidding?
Cheers.
This is so freaking good. I'm so happy
that our strawberry matcha is back. It's
just too perfect. Anyways, guys, I
actually did not do any of my makeup yet
aside from my lip gloss. So, let's go
finish up my makeup and then we're going
to get ready to go to lunch. Alrighty.
I'm going to throw my hair up. I always
do my hair just like this. Just grab it
any which way, claw clip it not
vertically but horizontally as such.
She's an icon. I'm just going to pin
rest of my hair back as I do my makeup.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Mattifying my face.
What?
>> Every day you're on the toilet. You're
not on the toilet.
>> on the toilet. I'm getting beautiful.
[music]
>> Oh my gosh, you're getting beautiful.
You're already beautiful.
>> Thank you. Anyhoo, I was saying we're
going to go [music] get some coffee
together right now. Even though I do
make most of my matchas at home, I do
still love going to cafe.
>> What was that? You love coffee?
>> I said I love going to cafe. Okay, I
actually do kind of like coffee. I like
matcha at home. Sorry. Kelly, let's do a
boyfriend voices over my makeup routine
video.
>> Okay, so putting down this palette of
powder then I'm wiping it on my face
like an artist. Circular motions because
I'm built like that. A couple down
motions on the nose. Oh, going to the
forehead because I got a big forehead.
Then I look off to my left because I see
my beautiful boyfriend. Mmm,
he's so beautiful. I can't hold myself
together. I have to show full teeth.
Next up, I'm putting on a blush because
I like to look like a princess. You
know, like [music]
in the movies they always have really
rosy cheeks. Next up, I'm putting on I
have no idea. Maybe these are sparkles.
I can't even tell. Oh, it's eyeliner.
She's putting on eyeliner.
Very little amount. I'm using my ring
finger because yeah, I want a ring on
it. You know what I'm saying?
Anyways, guys, I'm just so pumped for my
day. Like, can you believe that I have
this amazing boyfriend that I'm going to
go to Brooklyn with? Oh my gosh, he's
going to protect me.
>> Wait, I do get something. I'll be right
back. Let's see what we get in there.
>> Play elevator music.
Next up, we have a lip liner. This is
Fenty Beauty's shade of RiRi.
Shade of RiRi? Bro, I'm not my boyfriend
thinks I have really big lips. And then,
oh, this is my favorite thing. There's
something inside, I think. Which is a
lip gloss. Oh my gosh. Did someone say
that's a gloss balm in the shade of
Fussy? Y'all try to play with me? Nah,
check out my lips.
>> Perfect. Okay, well now Kelly and I are
going to go get coffee.
>> I've already had such an amazing day.
This is amazing.
>> Let's go.
I'm out.
>> I'm out.
>> [music]
[music]
[laughter]
>> You're so funny. Literally everything
that's hilarious.
Bro, they're fresh out of all the
sandwiches. No.
Off to the next bakery because our
favorite bakery was all out of
sandwiches. Quick break to [music] look
at the skyline.
>> [music]
>> I mean Hugh, this is not so good.
>> Good, good. We're good reaction right
now.
>> Hey, y'all. Uh you might be wondering
why it is a little bit dark out and that
is because I have been sitting right
here working on my computer for the last
4 hours. Well, time flies, guys. It
literally went from being like 4:00 p.m.
to now 8:33 p.m. And I have just been
working away on my computer. I guess in
case you're wondering what I'm working
on, I can absolutely [music] tell you.
First of all, I was of course working on
getting my [music] Fenty photos all
sorted, which by the way, the digitals
as well as the film came in and I'm so
excited. The photos actually [music]
look amazing. I can give you guys a
little sneak peek or actually you might
have probably seen them by now if you
follow [music] me on Instagram or if
you've clicked through and looked at the
Nami website. It's like right on the
product page. Like I said, I will have a
link down below in my description. We do
all of our talking back and forth on
Slack. So I spend a lot of hours just
like logged into Slack. Might be
triggering for some of YOU GUYS THAT
>> [screaming]
>> WORK CORPORATE JOBS. And also whenever I
have time, I like to kind of look for
more copyright free music that I can use
in my YouTube videos. And sometimes like
when I hear them, it helps me be more
inspired for how I can edit different
intros or different like segments in
upcoming videos, for example,
should you really buy
>> [music]
>> the Fenty x Nami Matcha collab?
Is the shade Fussy really that good?
And really that universal?
We'll see today. You guys know what I
mean. I also keep a planner / a journal.
I need this to be a journal where I can
actually write anything from my video
ideas to like literally just anything.
Ever to do. Upload Fenty photos. Oh,
upload this video.
Clothes to the thrift store. I have to
make a thumbnail for this video and one
of my other videos that I'm posting. And
that's all I can think of for now. Um,
let's go to dinner.
Or grocery shopping because we're going
to make dinner at home tonight. We're
going to have tacos and it's going to be
uh, amazing. So let's go grocery
shopping together with my friend Kelly
behind the camera for After Dynamics.
>> Hi, I'm Kelly. I'm her friend.
>> That's my friend. Okay, let's go for
some ingredients.
We're making some delicious and fresh
tacos, so you need a radish.
>> Wait, do you want me to film this part?
>> I meant this is the cabbage, shredded
carrots,
>> [music]
>> okay? Corn tortillas as well as
flour tortillas.
>> I like flour.
>> I like the corn. That's why we're
perfect for each other. I love you so
much.
>> I love you so much.
>> Okay, now we're going to choose an
avocado, which you [music] can choose
with your amazing eyeballs that Kelly's
having a severe allergic reaction to
something in the air.
>> I'm in the mood to be on camera, but I'm
here.
>> You're not in the mood?
>> Cuz my eyes hurt so bad.
>> Okay, then I'll remove you from the
vlog.
Okay, I removed you from the vlog.
>> Okay, I feel better now.
I couldn't hear you.
>> These are so fire. Cilantro microgreens.
Okay, we're pretty much done.
>> hurt so bad.
>> Why? What happened to them?
>> I think I'm allergic to you.
Now she's putting on her lipstick to
rizz up other dudes.
>> No, I'm not. I'm actually getting ready
to fight you. Hold my earrings.
>> Oh my god, is that a thing? That's a
girl thing.
>> Yeah.
>> I could do it, too.
>> Actually, what you would say is hold my
beer. I would say hold my earrings.
>> No, I would actually go like this.
>> Kelly, you're so sweet.
Oh my god, I literally can't bring you
anywhere. Like
You keep me young. You keep me young.
Okay, and of course the most important
thing has to be super extra firm tofu,
or it's not going to have the amazing
texture that you need.
>> You like it [music] firm?
What about loving and respectful?
>> Okay, and now we're ready to make our
tacos. And I'm going to allow you to get
[music] one special snack on me.
>> Can I be in a Mr. Beast challenge, but
on your channel?
>> Yeah, yeah, let's do it. Quick, choose
one item in the next 30 seconds and I'll
buy it for you. I am Mr. Beast.
>> Oh, jet.
>> He's a runner.
Uh-oh, the counter is ticking down.
Oh my god, he's walking me in a circle.
Are you kidding me?
>> Sorry.
>> Kelly, stop. Oh, he's trying to prank.
Oh, I see.
>> Honestly, I didn't want to see how long
you'd walk with me.
They call these the fridge sigs.
>> No, the fridge sig is when you make a
cola and you like add lime and something
else. Actually sounds amazing.
>> I thought I should have just said diet
coke.
>> No, but you add lime. That's what we
need, we need limes. I almost forgot.
>> I almost forgot to unclench my butt.
>> Four limes.
>> Hey, watch this.
>> Oh my god, [music] that's impressive.
>> Follow me.
>> That was it actually, Aura. Everyone
comment down below if that was Aura or
not.
Step one is cutting your tofu.
Like this, and about this thick. So, I
actually [music] have two different
kinds of tofu here. This one will cook
up nicer.
Nice, we have a bunch of pans going.
Kelly's cooking his beef back there.
Next up is our radish. Oh my god, I keep
calling this a radish. Yeah, I'm just
going to cut it straight down the
middle.
Oh my god. Cut out the bottom stem, like
that. Okay, and then you're just going
to slice your radish this way.
We're going to put it into a big old
bowl.
>> [music]
>> A whole bag of sliced carrots. [music]
It's good to press down on the tofu to
get out some of the moisture, but the
already pressed ones are pretty dry. So,
I don't really need to press on them too
much. Okay, we'll see if the stainless
steel is already.
I literally can't.
>> [music]
>> LOL. Okay, now we're going to make our
very extremely [music] important sauce.
What we're going to do is we're going to
roll some limes to make sure we get out
some juice. [music] You need at least
maybe like three limes minimum, maybe
four.
Okay.
I'm also constantly checking on my tofu
and whatnot. The main thing [music]
you're going to need is mayo.
Okay, let's take some mayo. I'm going to
make a lot of sauce, so we're going to
take like this much mayo, okay?
Now we're going to take our lime,
put it like this.
We'll need at least one whole [music]
lime, but you can decide if you want
more lime than that. Now we want it to
be like a kind of orangey color, like a
nice orange [music] to buttermilk mayo
color. So, I'm going to add some
sriracha cuz I'm crazy.
Then I'm also going to add some paprika
for color as well. Just a little bit,
not too much cuz it's actually kind of
turns it brown. Onion powder and garlic
powder. You can be kind of heavy-handed
with these [music] for good measure.
And now we're going to mix it all
together. It might not look like it's
mixing at first because of the lime
juice. Just push forward, guys. Almost
forgot a very important ingredient, and
that is agave cuz you also want some
sweetness in the sauce. And we're going
to add a little bit of salt as well.
Perfect.
And sesame seeds.
And then you just kind of flip it and
let it get caramelized and delicious.
And the key is to do this on a low temp
so the soy sauce isn't burning too
badly.
Now for our coleslaw, I basically make
the same exact mayo sauce and then plop
it on the top. And it's the same exact
sauce. And then we're just going to mix
it all up. The best way to do this, if
[music] you wash your hands, is to use
your hands. You can really get it all
incorporated.
Let's try some.
Oh my god. I can't. Get out.
Here's how I cut the tofu. I cut it into
like little tiny strips, and it tastes
so good. Look at this cross section.
Finally, this is how you cook your
tortilla.
Bam. Do not use your fingers, use tongs.
>> [music]
>> And here is our beautiful taco spread.
We have our slaw, tofu, lime, Kelly's
beef, tortillas,
sauce, cilantro microgreens, and
avocado. Oh, and pickled red onion.
You're the luckiest boy ever.
>> Taco Tuesday.
It's actually a Friday tonight.
>> You're so good at making this, too.
>> Oh, this is like my recipe that I have
down. So, I'm like, don't even get in my
freaking way. Kelly tried to ask if he
could help. Not today.
Sauce. Kelly likes to go in with a lot
of microgreens. Give it a nice squeeze.
There's my taco plate. It looks crazy. I
like corn tortilla, Kelly likes a flour
tortilla.
>> I'm Japanese, you're Korean.
>> I like matcha, you like coffee.
>> I like big dogs, you like little dogs.
>> That's so true.
>> Cheers.
Mhm. So good.
>> Mhm.
>> It is so good.
>> So good. I would stub my toe 10 times as
hard as I can in order to continue to
eat this, you know, one day. 10 hard
times.
And this sauce is like unreal.
>> Wow, what a yummy dinner.
>> Literally insane. Ashley, you're goat.
>> Thank you.
>> Seriously, bro. I'm like, finally. Okay,
we stopped filming. I'm like, I'm comfy
comfy right now. Cuz that was a warm,
cuz I'm wearing that non-branded
sweatshirt.
>> Okay. Anyways, guys, thank you so much
for watching today's vlog. I'm going to
end the vlog right here. Make sure that
you go check out namimatcha.com. Go get
our amazing Fenty collab. Yes, it's
available now for a limited time. It has
my favorite matcha, it's my favorite lip
gloss, and it's amazing, and this is my
life. And we love you, and we will talk
to you guys later.
Bye.
>> [music]
[music]